Finding Aid for Ross School of Business (University of Michigan) Publications 1916-2013
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Sub-Unit Publications
  - Placement Office
    - Brochures
      - The Michigan Intern, undated (Box 19)
      - Placement Guide, 1976/77 (Box 19)
      - The Placement Office and Your Future, undated (Box 19)
      - Recruiter's Guide, undated (Box 19)
  - Program in International Business
    - Proceedings
      - Workshop in International Financial Management, 1971-1972 (Box 19)
    - Proposals
      - Support of the Program in International Business, 1965 (Box 19)
    - Reports
      - Impact II: Development Program for Foreign Executives, 1963 (Box 19)
  - Public Utility Executive Program
    - Bulletins
      - 1952-1979, 5 folders (Box 19)
    - Directories
      - Alumni Directory, 1951-1966 (Box 19)
    - Programs
      - Graduation Exercises 1951 (Box 19)
    - Yearbooks 1951-1952 (Box 19)
  - Tauber Manufacturing Institute
    - Brochures (Box 22)
  - School of Banking
    - Bulletins
      - 1954-1975, 2 folders (Box 19)
  - William Davidson Institute
    - Brochures 1996 (Box 19)
    - Newsletters
      - The Davidson Window, 1994-1998 (Box 19)
      - Transition
        - 1998-2001 (scattered issues) (Box 19)
    - Programs (Conference)
      - The Impact of Foreign Investment on Emerging Markets, 1999 (Box 19)
  - Women in Business Initiative (Box 22)
    - Miscellaneous
      (Includes report Women and the MBA: Gateway to Opportunity
- Topical Publications
  - Conferences
    - Directories
      - Blue Cross Blue Shield Michigan Alumni Group Directory
        - 1952/53-1963/64 (Box 19)
      - Real Estate Alumni of Michigan
        - 1960/61-1964/65 (Box 19)
    - Proceedings
      - Accounting Employers Conference 1948 (Box 19)
      - Annual Business Conference
        - 1971-1973, 2 folders (Box 19)
      - Annual Report Forum 1949-1950 (Box 19)
      - Michigan Real Estate Clinic 1951-1960 (Box 19)
      - Michigan Savings and Loan League Clinic 1953 (Box 19)
    - Programs
      - Accountant's Graduate Study Conference 1948-1966 (Box 19)
      - Advanced Management Program for Accounting and Finance Executives 1968-1969 (Box 19)
      - Advertising Conference 1954-1959 (Box 19)
      - Alumni Conference 1929-1963 (Box 19)
      - Annual Business Conference 1964-1975 (Box 20)
      - Annual Marketing Research Conference 1951-1953 (Box 20)
      - Annual Midwest Management Faculty Conference 1962 (Box 20)
      - Annual Real Estate Clinic 1950-1974 (Box 20)
      - Annual Real Estate Forum 1994 (Box 20)
      - Annual Reports Forum 1949-1950 (Box 20)
      - Bank Study Conference 1939-1967 (Box 20)
      - Certificate Program in Real Estate 1953-1971 (Box 20)
      - Certificate Program in Real Estate Recognition Exercises 1950-1973 (Box 20)
      - A Conference for Michigan Chapters of the National Secretaries Association 1951-1953 (Box 20)
      - Conference on Hospital Financial Management 1954-1965 (Box 20)
      - Conference on Sales Management 1953-1962 (Box 20)
      - Consumer Finance Management Study Course 1953-1960 (Box 20)
      - Cost Accounting Conference 1947-1953 (Box 20)
      - Detroit Controller's Group 1945-1950 (Box 20)
      - The Economic Outlook 1962-1966 (Box 20)
      - Fall Accounting Conference 1973-1977 (Box 20)
      - Federal Tax Lecture Series 1948-1954 (Box 20)
      - A Forum for Top Management 1986 (Box 20)
      - Hardware Sales Study Course 1951-1956 (Box 20)
      - The Global Leadership Program 1989 (Box 20)
      - Merchandising Conference 1949-1957 (Box 20)
      - Michigan Accounting Conference 1935-1971 (Box 20)
      - Michigan Cost Conference 1950-1952 (Box 20)
      - Michigan Society for Quality Control 1949-1952 (Box 20)
      - Miscellaneous 1938-1990 (Box 20)
      - Office Machines and Supplies 1948-1953 (Box 20)
      - Quality Control by Statistical Methods 1948-1959 (Box 20)
      - Real Estate Program 1968-1977 (Box 20)
      - Review Course for C.P.A. Candidates 1950-1952 (Box 20)
      - Savings and Loan League Clinic 1951-1954 (Box 20)
      - Tax Conference 1948-1952 (Box 20)
    - Yearbooks
      - AEP Management Training Program, 1962 (Box 20)
      - Blue Cross Blue Shield Management Development Program, 1962/63 (Box 20)
  - Development
    - Announcements 1996 (Box 20)
    - Brochures undated (Box 20)
    - Newsletters
      - Campaign Report, 1994 (Box 20)
      - Capital Campaign News, 1983-1984 (Box 20)
      - Honor Roll of Donors, 1992-1998 (Box 20)
  - Summer Session
    - Bulletins
      - 1925-1932 (Box 20)
  - Visiting Committee
    - Miscellaneous 1986-1989 (Box 20)
    - Reports
      - Meeting of the Visiting Committee, 1972 (Box 20)
- Student Publications
  - General Student Publications
    - Newsletters
      - Bus. Ad-visor, 1979 (Box 20)
      - Michigan Business Forum, 1987/88 vol. 1-12 (Box 20)
      - Phi Chi Theta Newsletter, 1958-1960 (Box 20)
      - Student News, 1977 (Box 20)
      - Xi-igan, 1946-1948 (Box 20)
  - Specific Student Organization Publications
    - Black Business Students Association
      - Brochures
        - Black Students at the University of Michigan School of Business Administration, [1973] (Box 19)
      - Directories
        - Resume Directory
          - 1975/1976-1977/1978 (Box 19)
      - Newsletters
        - The Business Collegian, 1985-1986 (Box 19)
      - Programs
        - Annual Alumni Conference 1991 (Box 19)
    - Society of Creative Business Minds
      - Journals
        - Emily, [2000] (Box 19)
    - International Business Club
      - IBC News, 1990 (Box 22)
    - University of Michigan Entrepreneurs
      - Keeping in Touch -- Making a Difference, 1984-1986 (Box 22)
- Archived Ross School of Business Website
  The Ross School of Business Archived Website series documents the academic programs, accomplishments, resources, events, and people at the Ross School of Business. Content includes important news and announcements, publications (such as newsletters and course catalogs), and information about admissions, curriculum, degree requirements, faculty, and the overall mission of the School. The website series is arranged chronologically, with captures from 2002 and 2003 stored on CD. Starting in 2010, this archived website will be captured on a regular, ongoing basis as part of the University of Michigan Web Archives, hosted at http://webarchives.cdlib.org/a/universityofmichigan/.
  - Website capture May 15, 2002, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 2)
  - Website capture June 22, 2003, 1 optical disks CDs (Box 2)
  - Archived Stephen M. Ross School of Business home page 2010-[ongoing]
  - Archived websites related to the Ross School of Business 2010-[ongoing]